All right, welcome to
the next stage of
our YouTube pipe. And
in this phase, all
we're going to do
is look at fixing
the most common blockage
area in our sales
system, ideation and strategy.
And we're going to
do it in a
way that is easier,
more effective. It saves
you time. It earns
you more money. It
is quite literally the
only way to do
this if you want
to succeed. But the
weird thing is this.
For years, I have
been teaching YouTube. And
this, without doubt, has
been the most ignored
advice I ever give.
And it's also the
thing that I've had
the most emails about
where people are going,
Ed, I wish I
listened to you sooner.
I finally did what
you said and it
worked. And I could
never figure out why
would people skip the
easy thing until I
realized two things. Well,
it sounds too simple
to be true. And
then secondly, people try
it once, don't get
an instant result and
then go, No, it
won't work for me.
And they give up
and go back to
doing stuff that will
not work for them
in the long term.
So here's what I
need from you. If
you want to continue
your transformation into a
hulk of a channel
and business that you
are meant to become,
I need you to
stick to this plan
religiously for at least
40 videos before you
judge it. Why? Because
failing as fast as
you can is the
biggest part of this
process. I need you
to have a ton
of flops so we
can learn lessons from
them and then turn
them into wins. So
you have to remove
the emotion from this.
Do not write it
off as a strategy.
It doesn't work in
your niche. Do not
write it off as
only working for Ed.
Don't blame. Don't blame
your audience for not
wanting it. Just fail
as fast as you
can and keep going.
This works. Okay, so
here's what we're going
to do together in
this phase to try
and remove your blockage.
To start, we're going
to learn the overall
strategy we're going to
teach you. We're then
going to research your
niche to find patterns
that are going to
grow your channel. We're
then going to turn
those patterns into video
ideas that people actually
want. And then you're
going to use that
research to plan three
to four video thumbnails
and titles. And that's
it. All right, so
move on to the
next video where we're
going to start learning
about how strategy works.